{
    "subject": "resource/Ace_in_the_Hole_Band",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "The hometown of Ace in the Hole Band is United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9082545638084412,
            "question": "Is Ace in the Hole Band an American band?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.901901364326477,
            "question": "Can we say Ace in the Hole Band is an American band?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8260113596916199,
            "question": "Is the United States the primary location of Ace in the Hole Band's operations?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7933202385902405,
            "question": "Ace in the Hole Band's hometown is a part of which continent?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7635422348976135,
            "question": "Where is Ace in the Hole Band from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6616562008857727,
            "question": "Where did Ace in the Hole Band originate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5852733254432678,
            "question": "What is the nationality of Ace in the Hole Band?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5720135569572449,
            "question": "In which country was Ace in the Hole Band formed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47382664680480957,
            "question": "What country is Ace in the Hole Band based in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46527135372161865,
            "question": "What is the geographical origin of Ace in the Hole Band?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The hometown of Ace in the Hole Band is United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8911_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What country is Ace in the Hole Band based in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8911_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In which country was Ace in the Hole Band formed?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8911_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the nationality of Ace in the Hole Band?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8911_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8911_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8911_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8911_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8911_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8911_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8911_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8911_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8911_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8911_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8911_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\n**Explanation:** According to the documents, the members of the Ace in the Hole Band were originally students at Southwest Texas State University (now Texas State University), which implies that their hometown was the United States. Therefore, the statement \"The hometown of Ace in the Hole Band is United States\" is supported by the provided context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}